(Leonard:)- Sheldon, we have to do this.
- No, we don't.
(Sheldon:)We have to take in nourishment,
expel waste...
(Sheldon:)...and inhale enough oxygen
to keep our cells from dying.
(Sheldon:)Everything else is optional.
Okay, let me put it this way: I'm doing it.
(Sheldon:)You can't. I'm the lead author.
(Leonard:)Come on, the only reason you're the lead
author is because we went alphabetically.
(Sheldon:)I let you think we went alphabetically...
...to spare you dealing
with the fact that it was my idea.
(Sheldon:)Not to put too fine a point on it,
but I was throwing you a bone.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, I designed the experiment
that proved the hypothesis.
(Sheldon:)It doesn't need proving.
(Leonard:)So the entire scientific community
is just supposed to just take your word?
(Sheldon:)They're not supposed to,
but they should.
(Leonard:)I don't care what you say.
(Leonard:)I'm going to the conference,
presenting our findings.
(Sheldon:)And I forbid it.
(Leonard:)You forbid it?
(Sheldon:)If I'm not taking credit for our work,
then nobody is.
- So you admit that it's our work?
- No, once again, I'm throwing you a bone.
(Sheldon:)And once again, you are welcome.